<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8" createdIn="OpenLP 2.4.6" modifiedIn="OpenLP 2.4.6" modifiedDate="2021-01-09T02:52:49">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>All That I Have Lies In My Brother</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Author Unknown</author>
    </authors>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>All that I have lies in my brother,<br/>So when the going gets rough we have each other,<br/>And as we look to the cross we know its death,<br/>But there's a greater life beyond,<br/>When we walk by faith and not by sight.<br/>Chorus:<br/>We walk by faith and not by sight,<br/>We walk together hand in hand,<br/>To give strength to each other,<br/>When the flesh would say turn back!<br/>We walk this narrow way to the cross.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>As we walk down this narrow road,<br/>We lose many ones we love,<br/>But as all heavens and earth look down at us,<br/>All creation is rejoicing just waiting to be set free,<br/>For God has a people determined to go all the way,<br/>For they walk by faith and not by sight.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>As the sons of God go marching down this road,<br/>Each bearing the burdens of the others,<br/>They sing the songs of Zion,<br/>With victory in their hearts,<br/>For they're walking as one man,<br/>For they walk by faith and not by sight.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>Beloved, let us walk this way,<br/>Let us give glory in all things,<br/>For He shall surely lead us,<br/>Man's wisdom is God's foolishness,<br/>For there is glory in the cross,<br/>And the cross is our life,<br/>For we walk by faith and not by sight. </lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>Andoamos por fe por vista no,<br/>andamos unidos de la mano,<br/>para darnos fuerza el uno al otro<br/>cuando la carne se quiere devolver,<br/>andamos en el camino a la cruz.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>Todo lo que tengo está en mi hermano,<br/>si difícil es andar nos ayudamos<br/>y así mirando a la cruz,<br/>sabemos que es muerte, pero mayor es la vida,<br/>cuando andamos por fe y por vista no.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v7">
      <lines>Así al andar por este camino<br/>perdemos a muchos de los que amamos,<br/>más como el cielo y la tierra viendo están<br/>la creación se regocija esperando su libertad,<br/>pues Dios tiene un pueblo que irá hasta el fin,<br/>pues anda por fe y por vista no.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v8">
      <lines>Así los hijos de Dios caminan ya<br/>llevando las cargas el uno del otro,<br/>cantando los cánticos de Sión<br/>con victoria en sus corazones,<br/>pues lo están caminando, como un solo hombre<br/>pues caminan por fe y por vista no.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v9">
      <lines>Amados, andemos en este camino,<br/>en todo glorificando a Dios. Su vida es luz segura,<br/>el sabio es tonto ante Dios, pues hay gloria en la cruz<br/>y la cruz es nuestra vida, si andamos por fe por vista no.</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
