<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8" createdIn="OpenLP 2.4.6" modifiedIn="OpenLP 2.4.6" modifiedDate="2021-01-09T02:53:04">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>Born In A Stable, His Mother A Virgin</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Author Unknown</author>
    </authors>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>Born in a stable, His mother a virgin<br/>Raised in a carpenter's shop.<br/>His people were slaves; His parents were poor;<br/>His friends were a lowly lot.<br/>His chances in life were very slim;<br/>He's expected to be a slave.<br/>But people in darkness saw a light in Him,<br/>And the hope of freedom He gave.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>All of the power in heaven and earth<br/>God has invested in Him.<br/>He's to die on a cross, descend into hell,<br/>Meet the devil, take the keys from him.<br/>He yielded Himself to the death of the cross,<br/>Cried it's finished and slumped to die.<br/>In the regions of hell the devils celebrated,<br/>We've destroyed the King, they cried.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>In the midst of the celebration, footsteps were heard<br/>Walking the corridors of hell.<br/>The shouting stopped when a voice rang out,<br/>A voice that rang like a bell.<br/>Satan then trembled as they recognized Him<br/>Who came to deliver His own<br/>Shut and lock those gates he cried<br/>Don't let Him ascend to the throne.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>The the gates swung shut in the face of the King<br/>To proved God's salvation untrue.<br/>But He shook hell's gates and cried lift up your heads<br/>The King is coming through.<br/>Out of the devil's prison house came a procession<br/>Led by the King, Shouting, now O grave where is thy victory<br/>O death where is thy sting?<br/>Who is this King of glory? The Lord God mighty in battle is He.<br/>Who is this King of glory? The Master of the host of heaven.<br/>Supreme. The one who not even death could stop.<br/>Who is this King of glory?<br/>The little boy from the carpenter's shop.<br/>The little boy from the carpenter's shop.<br/>The little boy from the carpenter's shop.</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
