<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8" createdIn="OpenLP 2.4.6" modifiedIn="OpenLP 2.4.6" modifiedDate="2021-01-09T02:53:07">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>can you hear the kinsman's cry</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Author Unknown</author>
    </authors>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>Can you hear the Kinsman's cry<br/>As He's calling forth His bride:<br/>Can you feel the yearning deep within<br/>To draw you to His side:<br/>Are you listening to the voice that says, <br/>In me you shall abide:<br/>Will you go, will you go, will you go<br/>And be made as one? Drawn into the love union<br/>Thy Kinsman calleth now,<br/>Will you go, will you go, will you go?</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>Thou shalt pure and holy be, <br/>There shall be no spot in thee.<br/>I will give to thee my Name,<br/>And we'll be one and the same.<br/>Arise, my love, my fair one<br/>For thy Kinsman draweth nigh.<br/>Will you answer when He calls you,<br/>Will you go, will you go,<br/>Will you go and be made as one<br/>Drawn into the love union.<br/>Thy Kinsman calleth now,<br/>Will you go, will you go, will you go?</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>Is your heart in preparation <br/>For the day that He may call:<br/>To forsake all things behind you<br/>And to give to Him your all:<br/>Are you willing to be covered<br/>And to honor and obey:<br/>When He calls you will you answer,<br/>I will go, I will go,<br/>I will go and be made as one<br/>Drawn into the love union.<br/>Thy Kinsman calleth now,<br/>Will you go, will you go, will you go?</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>I have heard the Kinsman's cry<br/>Calling forth His perfect bride<br/>I can feel the yearning deep within <br/>To draw her to His side.<br/>I am listening to the voice that says, <br/>In me, you shall abide.<br/>I am ready, I am willing, I will go, I will go,<br/>I will go and be made as one<br/>Drawn into the love union.<br/>My Kinsman calleth now I will go, I will go, I will go.</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
