<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>Gird Yourself, Arise Unto The Battle</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Author Unknown</author>
    </authors>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>Gird yourself, arise unto the battle,<br/>Vested in the armor of the faith.<br/>Fear not, the God of hosts doth go before;<br/>This battle shall be the Lord's.<br/>Chorus:<br/>If our God hath delighted over us,<br/>If He hath seen us willing day by day to serve,<br/>If He find in us a humble and a contrite heart,<br/>Surrendered unto Him without reserve,<br/>Casting off the sin that did beset us,<br/>With its bitterness, resentments, and distress,<br/>Exalting Him above our vain ambitions,<br/>Till our ev'ry thought His lordship doth confess.<br/>Then, surely, God shall hear us from the heavens;<br/>His mercy and His power shall descend,<br/>And our Champion shall win for us the victory,<br/>Our inheritance of promise,<br/>Canaan land.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>Fear not the giants who oppose you,<br/>Intending to dispossess you of your hope.<br/>For their help hath forsaken the foes of the Lord,<br/>But our God shall fight in our midst. </lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>Levántate, sube a la batalla<br/>Ponte la armadura de la fe<br/>No dudes, es Dios quien te acompaña<br/>La victoria al final será de El.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>Si Jehová se agradare de nosotros<br/>Si no hallare en nosotros rebelión<br/>Si encontrase un corazón humilde<br/>Que se entrega a El sin condición<br/>Olvidándose de todo su pasado<br/>Amarguras, rencores y dolor<br/>Que le ama más que a sus caminos<br/>Y en sus vidas sólo es el Señor<br/>Entonces El oirá desde los cielos <br/>Su gracia y su poder descenderán<br/>Y Jehová nos entregará la tierra<br/>Nuestra herencia prometida Canaán</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>No temas porque hay gigantes<br/>Queriendo arrebatarte tu heredad<br/>Pues su amparo se apartó de ellos<br/>Mas Dios con nosotros está.</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
