<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>God was at work in the garden,</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Andrew Giles</author>
    </authors>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>God was at work in the garden,<br/>Creation was hardly begun;<br/>He took some earth and He shaped it<br/>To fashion a created son;<br/>Adam lay lifeless and empty<br/>At the end of creation's sixth day,<br/>When God breathed His breath in his nostrils<br/>Putting treasure in vessels of clay.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>CHORUS<br/>Treasures in vessels of clay,<br/>Riches in jars made of earth;<br/>If you never look past the external<br/>You'll never behold their true worth.<br/>For God has put in us His spirit<br/>His life and His truth there to stay,<br/>And though we're not much on the outside<br/>We are treasure in vessels of clay.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>The Midianites covered the valley<br/>An army dreadful in might;<br/>Gideon with three hundred soldiers<br/>Surrounded their camp in the night.<br/>The blast on the trumpet was sounded<br/>'The sword of the Lord,' they did say;<br/>Light shone from their pitchers, now broken<br/>For the treasure's in vessels of clay.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>Adam abandoned his treasure<br/>No more did he know divine breath:<br/>A Saviour was needed from heaven<br/>To ransom our souls out of death.<br/>Jesus was sent by His Father<br/>The price for rebellion to pay;<br/>Though many did not recognise it<br/>He was treasure in a vessel of clay.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>As history continues its progress<br/>Creation is groaning so loud.<br/>The poor and the weak are neglected<br/>For the rich and the strong are so proud;<br/>But God is raising a people,<br/>His kingdom will soon hold full sway<br/>And He'll free the travailing creation<br/>Using treasure from vessels of clay.<br/></lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
