<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>He Giveth More Grace When The Burdens Grow Greater</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Annie Johnson Flint</author>
    </authors>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>He giveth more grace when the burdens grow greater.<br/>He sendeth more strength when the labors increase.<br/>To added afflictions He addeth His mercies,<br/>To multiplied trials, His multiplied peace.<br/>Chorus:<br/>His love has no limit.<br/>His grace has no measure.<br/>His power no boundery known unto man.<br/>For out of His infinite riches in Jesus<br/>He giveth, and giveth, and giveth again.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>When we have exhausted our store of endurance.<br/>When our strength has failed 'ere the day is half done.<br/>When we reach the end of our hoarded resources,<br/>Our Father's full giving is only begun.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>Fear not that thy need shall exceed His provision,<br/>Our God ever yearns His resources to share;<br/>Lean hard on the arm everlasting, availing;<br/>The Father both thee and thy load will upbear.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>Su gracia es mayor, si las pruebas aumentan<br/>Su gracia es mayor, si la lucha es más cruel<br/>Si grande es la lucha, mayor es su gracia <br/>Si grande es la prueba, su amor es más fiel</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>Su amor no termina, su gracia no acaba <br/>Un límite no hay al amor de Jesús <br/>Pues de sus inmensas riquezas en gloria<br/>Abundan sus dones, abunda su amor </lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>Si a veces las noches, se tornan oscuras<br/>Y el cielo de bronce, parece que es<br/>No te desanimes, El está a tu lado <br/>Y aunque no le veas, su amor siempre es fiel</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
