<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8" createdIn="OpenLP 2.4.6" modifiedIn="OpenLP 2.4.6" modifiedDate="2021-01-09T02:54:55">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>It's Covered, Covered, Covered By The Blood Of The Lamb</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Author Unknown</author>
    </authors>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>Moses left old Pharaoh down in Egypt land,<br/>The Israelites delivered by God's almighty hand.<br/>They came up to the Red Sea and saw the way was blocked.<br/>The Israelites were running round in shock<br/>Chorus:<br/>It's covered, covered, covered by the Blood of the Lamb.<br/>Covered, covered, covered by the Blood of the Lamb.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>Moses cried out to the Lord, Lord what shall we do?<br/>Jehovah answered Moses, Man what's wrong with you?<br/>See that rod that's in your hand? Lift it up on high.<br/>Red Seas gonna open up, and Pharaoh's gonna die. </lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>Now David and Goliath were champions of old,<br/>Of Israelites and Philistines, the way the story's told.<br/>Goliath thought he had it made 'cause David was so small<br/>And he himself was over ten feet tall.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>Goliath said to David, You're nothing but a boy<br/>Come up to me and you will see I'll break you like a toy<br/>David said, I'll bury you beneath six feet of sod<br/>For you come to me with sword and shield<br/>But I come in the name of my God.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>Now, Jesus went to Calvary, it seemed that all was lost.<br/>Satan and his evil crew had nailed Him to the Cross.<br/>He looked up to the heavens and he said, Thy will be done.<br/>And ever since that day, for us the victory has been won.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>And now the Babylonish Church, she says I have to die.<br/>She tells me that my only hope is far beyond the sky.<br/>That sickness is my portion and the rapture is my hope.<br/>She expects me to believe that stuff as if I were a dope.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v7">
      <lines>For Romans eight has set me straight and filled my heart with glee,<br/>For the law of the Spirit of life, from sin and death has set me free.<br/>And now we sing, I shall be changed! and all the heavens ring.<br/>O grave where is thy victory! O death where is thy sting!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v8">
      <lines>Cubierto, cubierto, cubierto por la sangre de Jesus.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v9">
      <lines>David de los Israelitas y Goliat de los Filisteos,<br/>Cada uno fue campeon, asi lo entendemos.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v10">
      <lines>Goliat penso: Lo matare en un ya,<br/>Facilito eso sera, el israelita pequeno se ve,<br/>Y con mis dies metros ni batalla habra.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v11">
      <lines>Goliat diho a David: Un ninito eres tu para mi.<br/>Te hago pedasos como un huguete<br/>Si es que tu subes aqui.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v12">
      <lines>David le dijo: Abajo y muerto, alli te tocara estar.<br/>Pues to vienes con lanza y espada<br/>Mas yo en el nombre de Jehova.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v13">
      <lines>Moises estaba con ese Faraon en Egipto y alli lo dejo</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v14">
      <lines>La mano poderosa del Senor a los Israelitas lo liberto.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v15">
      <lines>Llegaron al mar rojo y el camino se cerro alli<br/>Muertos de miedo, confusos y atonitos</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v16">
      <lines>Y casi se desmayan alli.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v17">
      <lines>Moises clamo al Senor: Dios mio que acemos aqui?</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v18">
      <lines>Jehova contesto a Moises: Porque estas asi?<br/>No ves la vara en tu mano?, levantala arriba ya</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v19">
      <lines>Y veras que el mar se abre y faraon si morira.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v20">
      <lines>El caso paresido perdido cuando Jesus al Calverio llego<br/>Satanas con su ejercito a una cruz le clavo</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v21">
      <lines>Sea hecha tu voluntad, dijo Jesus, y a los cielos el miro<br/>Desde entonces podemos vencer</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v22">
      <lines>Porque la victoria el gano.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v23">
      <lines>La iglesia babilonia dice: Seguro que moriras<br/>Que mi unica esperanza esta enlos cielos, mas alla</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v24">
      <lines>Que la enfermedad es mi porcion y que y que a los cielos ire yo </lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v25">
      <lines>Y espera que yo coma ese cuento como si un tonto fuera</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v26">
      <lines>Yo Romanos 8 me ha enderezado y mi corazon <br/>Esta alegre en mi y ahora el Espirito de vida me ha</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v27">
      <lines>Liberado de la muerte, si.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v28">
      <lines>Y ahora cantamos: Seremos transformados.<br/>Y en los cielos estan cantando ya:</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v29">
      <lines>Donde esta, oh muerte, tu aguijon?</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
