<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>May All Who Come Behind Us Find Us Faithful</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Author Unknown</author>
    </authors>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>Chorus:<br/>May all who come behind us find us faithful.<br/>May the fire of our devotion light their way.<br/>May the footprints that we leave<br/>Lead them to believe,<br/>And the lives we live inspire them to obey.<br/>May all who come behind us find us faithful.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>We're pilgrims on the journey<br/>Of the narrow road.<br/>And those who've gone before us line the way.<br/>Cheering on the faithful, encouraging the weary,<br/>Their lives a stirring testament to God's sustaining grace.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>Surrounded by so great a cloud of witnesses,<br/>Let us run the race not only for the prize.<br/>But as those who've gone before us,<br/>Let us leave to those behind us<br/>The heritage of faithfulness passed on through godly lives.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>After all our hopes and dreams have come and gone,<br/>And our children sift through all we've left behind.<br/>May the clues that they discover and the memories they uncover<br/>Become the light that leads them to the road we each must find.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>Peregrinos somos por este camino<br/>y los que nos preceden, nos lo muestran<br/>animando a los fieles, alentando a los cansados<br/>sus vidas testimonio vivo por la gracia de Dios.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>Oh! que nuestro Dios nos encuentre fieles<br/>y que el fuego de nuestra entrega de luz.<br/>Que las huellas que dejemos induzcan a creer,<br/>que nuestras vidas inspiren obedecer.<br/>Oh! que nuestro Dios, nos encuentre fieles.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v7">
      <lines>Rodeados por tan grande nube de testigos,<br/>corramos para conseguir el premio.<br/>Como aquellos que nos preceden<br/>sigamos con los que vienen,<br/>a la heredad de fidelidad que nos mostraron ya.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v8">
      <lines>Poniendo nuestros ojos en nuestro Señor,<br/>considerando a él que así sufrió.<br/>Que nuestro ánimo no desmaye<br/>y nuestra fe no se apague,<br/>despojándonos de todo peso de pecado ya.</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
