<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8" createdIn="OpenLP 2.4.6" modifiedIn="OpenLP 2.4.6" modifiedDate="2021-01-09T02:55:43">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>Neither Do I Condemn Thee, Precious Words Divine</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Author Unknown</author>
    </authors>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>Neither do I condemn thee, precious words divine,<br/>From the lips of mercy, like the sweetest chime<br/>Wonderful words of Jesus, sing them o'er and o'er<br/>Neither do I condemn thee, go and sin no more</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>By a crowd of worshippers sorry for their sins<br/>Came a lowly stranger, rudely brought in <br/>Scribes came and Pharisees anxious to see<br/>What that meek Nazarene's verdict would be</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>They told of her wanderings marking each flaw<br/>Spoke of her punishment, quoting the law<br/>Writing upon the ground, sadly and slow<br/>Spoke he unheedingly, head bended low</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>Still cried the Pharisees, Pray, master pray<br/>What shall we do with her, what dost thou say?<br/>Then said He rebuking them let the first throw<br/>Come from the sinless hand, he that sins no more.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>Cheeks blushing with the shame, turning about<br/>And from His presence walked slowly out<br/>Then they saw Him standing there, head bended low<br/>He whom the world despised bade her sin no more</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>Spoke He most tenderly, Pray, woman pray<br/>Hast thou no accusers? Nay, master nay<br/>Neither do I condemn thee, soul sick and sore<br/>Go forth I have pardoned thee, go and sin no more. </lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v7">
      <lines>Ni yo te condeno palabra de Dios<br/>Desde su trono al mundo pecador<br/>Ni yo te condeno palabra de amor<br/>Ni yo te condeno ve y no peques más.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v8">
      <lines>Un gran número de pueblo<br/>De pecado en confusión<br/>Vino una desconocida<br/>Traída sin compasión<br/>Ante escribas y fariseos<br/>Ansiosos por oír<br/>El veredicto del Nazareno<br/>En el caso de la mujer.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v9">
      <lines>Dijeron los fariseos:<br/>Maestro, Qué nos dirás?<br/>Qué debemos hacer con ella,<br/>En qué camino seguirá?<br/>Les dijo reprendiéndoles:<br/>La primera piedra que venga <br/>De la mano que no ha pecado<br/>Y del que pecado no tenga.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v10">
      <lines>Hablaron de sus desvíos<br/>Las faltas anotaron,<br/>Hablaron de sus castigos,<br/>La ley ellos citaron;<br/>Lentamente El escribiendo<br/>En la tierra cuando hablaban<br/>Dijo estas palabras la cabeza inclinada.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v11">
      <lines>De vergüenza confundidos<br/>Voltearon así<br/>Le vieron parado en su lugar<br/>Orando por los demás<br/>Despreciado por el pueblo<br/>Le dijo no peques más.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v12">
      <lines>Tiernamente le dijo El<br/>Mujer: Qué me dices,  <br/>acusadores ya no hay para ti?<br/>No, maestro, ninguno me sigue<br/>Ni yo te condeno<br/>Como hicieron los demás<br/>Vete, yo te perdono<br/>Vete y no peques más.</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
