<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>One Day Closer To The Kingdom</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Author Unknown</author>
    </authors>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>One day closer to the kingdom.<br/>That makes every day a little better than the day before.<br/>I can take another step, knowing that tomorrow,<br/>I'll be one day closer to the shore.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>Sometimes I think I just can't take another step.<br/>The storms of life keep raging o'er and o'er.<br/>But something down in my heart,<br/>makes me want to keep on walking.<br/>I'll be one step closer to the shore.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>There's something in me that can't go back again.<br/>There's something in me that can't go back again.<br/>Well Satan can tempt, and Satan can test,<br/>And every day he will do his best,<br/>But there's something in me that can't go back again.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>There's something in me that's got to keep moving on.<br/>There's something in me that's got to keep moving on.<br/>The King of Kings, who reigns in me,<br/>Is singing songs of victory,<br/>And there's something in me that's got to keep moving on.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>Un paso más cerca al reino<br/>Y cada día es un poco más lleno de paz,<br/>Este día puedo andar<br/>Sabiendo que mañana <br/>Estaré cerca del reino un paso más</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>A veces pienso, ya no puedo andar<br/>Y quiero pararme y descansar<br/>Más algo muy adentro me hace seguir andando<br/>Y estaré cerca al Reino un paso más.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v7">
      <lines>/Hay algo en mí que no puede volver atrás/ (2)<br/>Satanás me puede tentar, me puede probar<br/>Y cada día me puede hablar<br/>Mas hay algo en mí que no puede volver atrás</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v8">
      <lines>/Hay algo en mí que adelante va a seguir/ (2)<br/>El Rey de reyes que reina ya<br/>Y en cada batalla cantará<br/>Más hay algo en mí que adelante va a seguir</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
