<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>T'was A Day In Early Springtime</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Author Unknown</author>
    </authors>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>T'was a day in early springtime<br/>By an ancient wayside well<br/>Eliezer paused to rest his camel train<br/>He had found a bride for Isaac<br/>'Ere the evening shadows fell<br/>For his weary journey had not been in vain. <br/>Chorus:<br/>Oh, get ready, evening shadows fall<br/>Don't you hear the Eliezer call<br/>There's going to be a wedding<br/>Our joy will soon begin<br/>In the evening when the camel train comes in!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>So he took the fair Rebecca<br/>Decked with jewels rich and rare<br/>Back to Abraham and Isaac far away<br/>Where Rebecca loved her Isaac<br/>And he loved Rebecca fair<br/>Oh, it must have been a happy wedding day.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>Now the blessed Holy Spirit<br/>From the Father God above<br/>Has come back to earth to find a worthy bride<br/>For our Isaac over yonder<br/>Has prepared his tents of love<br/>And He wants His fair Rebecca by His side.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>We have left our Kinsfolk gladly<br/>We have bade the world good-bye<br/>We are going to a land beyond the sky<br/>Where we'll soon behold our Isaac<br/>In that blessed eternity<br/>What a happy, happy wedding that will be. </lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>Fue un día de primavera, en un pozo en el camino<br/>Eliecer paró su caravana a descansar<br/>Halló novia para Isaac, sombras de la noche caen<br/>Su cansado viaje inútil no lo fue</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>Oh prepárate sombras de la noche caen<br/>No oyes el llamado de Eliecer?<br/>Va ha haber una boda <br/>Nuestro gozo va a empezar<br/>En la noche al entrar la caravana.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v7">
      <lines>Así se llevó a Rebeca de mil joyas adornada<br/>Con Abraham e Isaac lejos de su hogar<br/>Donde Rebeca amó a Isaac e Isaac a su Rebeca<br/>Esta boda debió haber sido feliz.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v8">
      <lines>Ahora el Santo Espíritu de nuestro Padre Dios <br/>A la tierra una novia vino a buscar<br/>Pues Isaac ha preparado allá sus tiendas de amor<br/>A Rebeca a su lado desea tener.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v9">
      <lines>Dejamos nuestros parientes, dijimos al mundo adiós <br/>vamos a una tierra nueva espiritual<br/>Donde veremos a nuestro Isaac por la bendita eternidad<br/>Que feliz, feliz, feliz, boda será.</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
