<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8" createdIn="OpenLP 2.4.6" modifiedIn="OpenLP 2.4.6" modifiedDate="2021-01-09T02:56:57">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>The Voice Of My Beloved, Lo, He Comes</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Author Unknown</author>
    </authors>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>The voice of my Beloved, lo, He comes.<br/>The voice of my Beloved, lo, He comes.<br/>He's leaping over the mountains<br/>And skipping over the hills<br/>The voice of my Beloved, lo, He comes.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>The voice of my Beloved says to me.<br/>The voice of my Beloved says to me,<br/>Rise up, my love, fair one and comes away with me.<br/>The voice of my Beloved says to me.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>For lo, the winter is over and is past.<br/>For lo, the winter is over and is past.<br/>The flowers appear and the birds sing.<br/>And the voice of the turtle is heard,<br/>For lo, the winter is over and past.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>Who is this coming up from the wilderness?<br/>Who is this coming up from the wilderness?<br/>She's leaning on her Beloved for love is strong as death.<br/>Who is this coming up from the wilderness?</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>Many waters cannot quench love neither can the floods drown love.<br/>If a man give all that he has for love it would utterly be contemned.<br/>For many waters cannot quench love.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>The voice of my Beloved says to me.<br/>The voice of my Beloved says to me,<br/>Thou art all fair, my loved one, there is no spot in thee.<br/>The voice of my Beloved says to me. </lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v7">
      <lines>La voz de mi amado ya está<br/>La voz de mi amado ya está<br/>saltando sobre los montes<br/>brincando en los collados<br/>la voz de mi amado ya está.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v8">
      <lines>/La voz de mi amado me dice a mí/ (2)<br/>levántate mi paloma y huye ya conmigo<br/>la voz de mi amado me dice a mi.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v9">
      <lines>/Mis pecados son borrados ya/ (2)<br/>mi Jesús los sepultó en la más profunda mar<br/>mis pecados son borrados ya.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v10">
      <lines>/En un día nacerá una nación. / (2)<br/>cuando esté de parto Sión dará a luz<br/>en un día nacerá una nación.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v11">
      <lines>/Si Jesús viene al mundo otra vez/ (2)<br/>Satanás será hollado por los hijos del Señor<br/>Si Jesús viene al mundo otra vez.</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
