<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>Wonderful Peace</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>W. George Cooper Warren D. Cornell</author>
    </authors>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>Chorus:<br/>Peace, peace, wonderful peace.<br/>Coming down from the Father above.<br/>Sweep over my spirit forever I pray.<br/>In fathomless billows of love.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>Far away in the depths of my spirit tonight<br/>Rolls a melody sweeter than psalm;<br/>In celestial-like strains it unceasingly falls<br/>O’er my soul like an infinite calm.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>What a treasure I have in this wonderful peace,<br/>Buried deep in the heart of my soul,<br/>So secure that no power can mine it away,<br/>While the years of eternity roll!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>I am resting tonight in this wonderful peace,<br/>Resting sweetly in Jesus’ control;<br/>For I’m kept from all danger by night and by day,<br/>And His glory is flooding my soul!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>And I think when I rise to that city of peace,<br/>Where the Author of peace I shall see,<br/>That one strain of the song which the ransomed will sing<br/>In that heavenly kingdom will be:</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>Ah soul, are you here without comfort and rest,<br/>Marching down the rough pathway of time?<br/>Make Jesus your friend ere the shadows grow dark;<br/>Oh, accept this sweet peace so sublime!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v7">
      <lines>Coro: ¡Paz!, ¡paz!, ¡cuán dulce paz!<br/>es aquélla que el padre me da.<br/>Yo le ruego que inunde por siempre mi ser,<br/>en sus ondas de amor celestial.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v8">
      <lines>En el seno de mi alma una dulce quietud<br/>se difunde inundado mis er<br/>una calma infinita que sólo podrán<br/>los amados de Dios comprender.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v9">
      <lines>Qué tesoros yo tengo en la paz que me dio<br/>y en el fondo del alma ha de estar;<br/>tan segura que nadie quitarla podrá<br/>mientras miro los años pasar.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v10">
      <lines>Alma triste que en rudo conflicto te ves<br/>sola y débil tu senda a seguir,<br/>haz de Cristo tu amigo pues fiel siempre es<br/>y su paz tú podrás recibir.</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
